This 23-year-old white female presents with a complaint of allergies.
She used to have allergies when she lived in Seattle, but she thinks they are worse here.
In the past, she has tried Claritin and Zyrtec.
Both worked for a short time, but then seemed to lose effectiveness.
She had also used Allegra also.
She used the Plasmur and she began using it again two weeks ago.
It doesn't appear to be working very well. She has used over-the-counter sprays, but no prescription nasal sprays.
She does have asthma, but doesn't require daily medication for this
and does not think it is plaring up.
Her only medication currently is Orthoticycline and Allegra.
and allegra